JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 22
YOSHIKAGE KIRA JUST
WANTS TO LIVE QUIETLY, PART 2
HIGH SCHOOL AHEAD
NO MIDDLE SCHOOL STUDENTS
BEYOND THIS POINT
- MIDDLE SCHOOL PRINCIPAL
SHIGEKIYO YANGU: DECEASED
STAND: HARVEST
DEADLY QUEEN
CENTIPEDE SHOES
WE DO SIMPLE TAILORING
ANIMAL CRACKERS
KIRA
EPISODE 23
HEART ATTACK, PART 1